{
    "subject": "resource/Integra_Live",
    "predicate": "ontology/programmingLanguage",
    "object": "resource/Pure_Data",
    "human_readable": "Integra Live is programmed in Pure Data.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8954328894615173,
            "question": "How does Integra Live utilize Pure Data's features?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5552874207496643,
            "question": "What programming language is Integra Live written in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5439479947090149,
            "question": "What software environment is used to create Integra Live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5397926568984985,
            "question": "Is Pure Data a popular language for live performance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46290427446365356,
            "question": "What kind of applications can be built using Pure Data?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40666714310646057,
            "question": "Can you name a software tool similar to Pure Data?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.402902215719223,
            "question": "What are the strengths of using Pure Data for programming?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3441617488861084,
            "question": "Does Pure Data have a community of users and developers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27276965975761414,
            "question": "What are some examples of projects created with Pure Data?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20654326677322388,
            "question": "Are there any limitations to using Pure Data for development?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Integra Live is programmed in Pure Data.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8296_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some examples of projects created with Pure Data?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8296_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Pure Data have a community of users and developers?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8296_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the strengths of using Pure Data for programming?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8296_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8296_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8296_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8296_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8296_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8296_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8296_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8296_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8296_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8296_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8296_5.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that according to the context information, it is stated that \"Integra Live uses Pure Data as its signal processing engine...\" (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8296/re-ranker-msmarco/5.txt) and also mentioned in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8296/re-ranker-msmarco/19.txt that \"The Integra Live audio processing host runs in the Pure Data engine...\" which supports the triple that Integra Live is programmed in Pure Data."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Integra Live uses Pure Data as its signal processing engine, which supports the statement that it is programmed in Pure Data."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}